It's not what you think.
Tickled is a documentary film directed by David Farrier.
Journalist David Farrier stumbles upon a mysterious tickling competition online.
As he delves deeper he comes up against fierce resistance, but that doesn’t
stop him getting to the bottom of a story stranger than fiction.
Himself, played by David Farrier.
Himself, played by Dylan Reeve.
Himself, played by David Starr.
Himself, played by Hal Karp.
Himself, played by Marko Realmonte.
Himself, played by Kevin Clarke.
Tickled is a 2016 New Zealand documentary about "competitive endurance tickling" and
videos featuring it, and the practices of those producing the videos.
It is directed by David Farrier and Dylan Reeve.
The film explores possible legal and ethical issues with certain individuals making
the videos, and has itself been the subject of legal challenges.
A follow-up special, The Tickle King, aired on HBO in February 2017.
The film explores themes of journalist, sports,
secret identity, fetish, fetishism.
The tone is thought_provoking.